DevOps a set of practices to build test and release your code in small frequent
DevOps 一组实践，用于以小而频繁的
steps one of the core practices of DevOps is continuous integration which
步骤构建测试和发布代码 DevOps 的核心实践之一是持续集成，它
has developers commit their code to a shared repository often on a daily basis
让开发人员经常将他们的代码提交到共享存储库，
each commit triggers an automated workflow on a CI server that can notify
每次提交都会触发CI 上的自动化工作流 服务器可以
developers of any issues integrating their changes when a repo evolves in
在 repo 以这样的小步骤发展时通知开发人员集成他们的更改的任何问题
small steps like this it prevents what's known as merge Towel imagine Mary you're
它可以防止所谓的合并毛巾想象 Mary 你
back and developer builds a new API for your product
回来了，开发人员
shortly after Jane your front-end developer starts work on a new UI a few
在 Jane 你的前端开发人员之后不久为你的产品构建了一个新的 API 几个月后开始在新 UI 上工作，
months later when it comes time to merge their features we find that they're
当需要合并它们的功能时，我们发现它们
completely incompatible the build fails and we now have to spend a bunch of time
完全不兼容，构建失败，我们现在必须花费大量时间
and money resolving these conflicts let's go ahead and build a continuous
和金钱来解决这些冲突，让我们继续构建一个 持续
integration pipeline now to see how it prevents issues like this here on github
集成管道现在看看它如何在 github 上防止此类问题
I have a node.js web app in order to deliver this out to my customers I need
我有一个 node.js Web 应用程序，以便将其交付给我的客户
to run three commands test build and deploy I can automate this entire
需要运行三个命令测试构建和部署我可以
process in the cloud by using a CI service like github actions first I
通过使用像github操作这样的CI服务在云中自动化整个过程我首先
create a workflow and then I tell it to run on every push to the master branch
创建一个工作流然后我告诉它在每次推送到主分支时运行
the event triggers a job that runs on a Linux container in the cloud and we tell
事件触发一个工作 它在云中的 Linux 容器上运行，我们
the container what to do as a series of steps first it checks out the code in
通过一系列步骤告诉容器要做什么，首先它检查
this github repo then sets up nodejs installs my dependencies and runs my
这个 github repo 中的代码，然后设置 nodejs安装我的依赖项并运行我的
tests build and deploy commands now anytime we
测试，现在我们可以随时构建和部署命令
commit code to the master branch in this repo it will run this workflow if any of
将代码提交到此 repo 中的 master 分支，如果任何步骤失败，它将运行此工作流
the steps fail the bad software won't be delivered to our customers and will
，不良软件将不会交付给我们的客户，并且会
automatically know there's an issue that needs to be addressed at the end of the
自动知道有一个问题需要在一天结束时解决
day CI CD offers two main benefits it helps you automate things that would
CI  CD 提供了两个主要好处，它可以帮助您将
otherwise have to be done manually by developers that will increase your
原本必须由开发人员手动完成的事情自动化，这将提高您的
velocity but it also detects small problems early before they can grow into
速度，但它还可以在小问题发展为 majo 之前及早发现它们
major disasters and that results in higher code quality this has been C ICD
r 灾难并导致更高的代码质量这
or DevOps in 100 seconds make sure to hit the like button if you want to see
是 100 秒内的 C ICD 或 DevOps如果您想观看更多这样的短视频，请确保点击“赞”按钮，
more short videos like this and stay tuned tomorrow for a full dead loss
并在明天继续关注使用 github 操作的完整死损
project using github actions thanks for watching and I will see you in the next
项目谢谢观看，我会在下一个看到你
one